“番茄大战”凭借约140吨过熟西红柿
And with approximately 140 tons of overripened tomatoes,
稳居全球最盛大年度食物狂欢
La Tomatina remains the world's greatest annual food fight.
现在将镜头“扔回”演播室
Throwing it back to you at the studio.
我们稍后“再酱”
We'll ketchup later.
这太痛苦了
That was painful.
怎么 虽然这番茄“梗”没熟 但“藤”鲜的
What? All right, that wasn't my best tomato pun, but it was vine.
对不对 弗朗西斯
Wasn't it, Francis?
老大 你不用假装直播
You know, boss, you don't need to give a fake broadcast.
- 你知道我们是在执行任务吧  - 好吧 淡定
- You know we're on a mission, right? - Okay, easy.
你有你的办事方法 我有我的 简单
You have your process, I have mine. Simple.
现在什么也别说了 盯好格拉多夫
Now let's zip it and keep our eyes peeled for Gradov.
不过话说回来 库珀 我的番茄酱双关是不是还挺好的
Seriously, Coop, the "ketchup" line was strong, yeah?
诺埃尔 作为你认识最久的朋友
Noel, as your oldest friend,
我实名认证你的梗一点都不好笑
I can definitively say that was not punny.
所以我执行重要任务 必须带上你们中情局的人
That's why I don't go big game hunting without you CIA boys.
说起任务 我们发现了一个可疑人物
Speaking of, we got a lion in the crosshairs.
灰帽子 灰外套 粉衬衫 朝西南那边去了
Gray hat and jacket, pink shirt, heading southwest,
与目标描述相符
matching the target's description.
马上进行面部识别
Walk faces and run it.
好的 粉衬衫
Okay, pink shirt, pink shirt.
好了 拍到了
Okay, I got him.
但我无法确认这就是格拉多夫
But I can't confirm it's Gradov.
周 你那边有什么发现
Cho, you got anything?
不行
That's a negative.
面部识别不出来
No-go for facial recognition.
等等 他好像就在我眼前
Wait. I think I'm staring right at him.
离我20英尺 就在你下面 库珀
20 feet from me, right below you, Coop.
什么
What?
该死
Ah, shit.
伙计们 现场有两个 疑似格拉多夫的家伙
Guys, we got two potential Gradovs on site.
三个
Three.
该死
Shit.
他带了诱饵 盯好你那个 杰克斯
He's got decoys in play. Stay on your mark, Jacks.
报告最新情况 基地
Talk to me, home base.
面部识别还是不行 他们好像知道我们的摄像头位置
Still no facial recall. It's like they know where our cameras are positioned.
给我做步态分析
Get me gait analysis.
我们得申请“梯队监视系统”的补丁
We'd have to request a patch to Echelon.
那就赶紧申请补丁
Then request the patch!
亚当斯总监
Director Adams?
收到要求更新实时补丁的请求
We have a request for a real-time patch.
军情六处要联合中情局 抓捕一个高价值目标
It's a joint MI6-CIA capture of a high-value target.
- 有多高  - 国家安全局最高等级
- How high? - NSA priority.
是俄罗斯军火商维克托格拉多夫
Russian arms dealer Viktor Gradov.
两年多来第一次发现他的行踪
First sighting in over two years.
诺埃尔 一号目标仍在西南角
Noel, target one is still in the southwest corner.
库珀 这辆车感觉不妙
Coop, I don't like this van.
现场探员 你们被授权连接“梯队”服务器60秒
Field, you're authorized for a 60-second link to Echelon's servers.
够我锁定真正的格拉多夫了
All the time I need to pin the real Gradov.
是一辆大众T5 西班牙车牌
It's a VW T5, Spanish plates,
注册在马德里一家租赁公司名下
registered to a rental company in Madrid.
你到底是什么东西
What are you?
现场探员 任务中止 这是陷阱
Field team, abort! We've been set up!
搞定
Done.
不许动
Don't move.
放下
Drop it.
美国总统威廉德林杰
U.S. President Will Derringer,
近日国内外支持率持续飙升
amidst soaring popularity at home and abroad,
已于昨日到达伦敦
touched down in London yesterday.
德林杰在前往意大利参加北约峰会前
Derringer has stopped in the U.K. for a brief visit
将对英国进行短暂访问
before he heads to a NATO summit in Italy...
总统将与执政已六年...
...president will be attending a press
...但近期深陷困境的英国首相
conference in his first face-to-face meeting
萨姆克拉克举行首次面对面会晤
with the increasingly embattled  Prime Minister Sam Clarke,
并共同出席新闻发布会
now serving his sixth year in office...
德林杰凭借《水蟒》系列电影中 “丹宁毒液”一角
...Derringer smashed worldwide box office records playing the Venom in Denim
一举打破全球票房纪录
with his Water Cobra franchise.
然后从枪林弹雨的硬汉形象摇身一变
He then went from bullets flying to tears flowing
在催人泪下的棒球题材电影 《滑向本垒》中顺利完成银幕转型
with his heartfelt baseball drama Sliding into Home...
儿子 我们做到了
We did it, son.
妈妈一定很骄傲
Made Mom proud.
为他赢得了金球奖提名...
...earning him a Golden Globe nomination...
上任仅五个月后
After only five months in office,
德林杰的支持率和选民信任度 就创下历史新高
Derringer is enjoying historic polling numbers and voter confidence.
在你们的支持下 我们成功征服票房
With your help, we did it at the box office,
现在我们将征服椭圆办公室
and now we will do it at the Oval Office.
得了吧
No.
我们爱威廉
国家元首
本WEB版外挂字幕由  风吹来的那片云  双语合并
早安 首相先生
Good morning, Mr. Prime Minister.
这是您29号星期四的简报
Here's your brief for Thursday the 29th.
经济部长将宣布失业率创历史新低
The economic minister will announce record low unemployment.
波兰的难民危机继续加剧
The refugee crisis in Poland continues to intensify,
难民人数增加到数万人
with numbers growing into the tens of thousands.
您原定的早间会议已被取消 以便召开紧急简报会
Your early-morning meetings have been cleared
通报西班牙境内 以悲剧收场的机密情报行动
for an urgent briefing on a classified intelligence op in Spain that ended in tragedy.
七名中情局和军情六处特工被杀害
Seven CIA and MI6 operatives have been killed.
萨姆 很遗憾 诺埃尔比赛特队长失踪了
Sam, I regret to say that team leader Noel Bisset is missing
据推测已死亡
and presumed dead.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
已通知逝者家属
Families of the fallen are being
会见...
notified...
你没事吧 老大
You okay, boss?
在英国王室成员 接待美国总统及其家人之际...
And while the royals play host to the American president and his family,
...创纪录规模的人群聚集于此 只为目睹威廉德林杰的风采
record crowds are gathered, hoping for a glimpse of Will Derringer,
证明其在国外和国内一样深受爱戴
proving he's as loved abroad as he is at home.
我只是不明白 北风和这些有什么关系
I just don't understand what tornado has to do with anything.
不是北风 是北约 好吗
Not tornados. NATO, okay?
这些国家就好比一群朋友们
It's like, um, a-a group of friends. Let's say, in this case, countries.
聚在一起 勾勾小指 承诺有恶霸出现
They-they get together, and they make a pinky promise if they ever see a bully,
攻击其中一个朋友
let's say this guy, and the bully attacks one of them,
那他们就必须一起反抗这个恶霸
they all got to join in and stand up to that bully.
然后他们就开始朝额头扔弹头
And that's when they start dropping warheads on foreheads.
什么...嘿 什么
Hey, what?
谁让她看了《水蟒》
Who let her watch Water Cobra?
- 我在珍妮家看的 - 是吗
- I saw it at Janey's house. - Oh, you did?
好吧 这下珍妮的妈妈 要接受联邦调查了
Okay, well, Janey's mom is now under federal investigation.
先生
Sir.
快走
Scoot.
- 剑桥大学的讲座是几点  - 4点才开始
- What time's the lecture at Cambridge? - Not till 4:00.
- 早上在得里雅斯特见  - 好的
- Meet you at Trieste in the morning? - Yeah.
好好享受吧
Enjoy this.
趁机和首相搞好关系
And use it as a bonding opportunity with the prime minister.
拜托
Please.
别告诉我你还在为炸鱼薯条的事生气
Don't tell me you're still mad about the fish and chips thing.
他在竞选期间支持了我的对手
He endorsed my opponent in the heat of the campaign.
他只是和那人吃了个午饭 这可算不上支持
He had lunch with the guy. It's hardly an endorsement.
不是普通午饭
Wasn't just lunch.
那可是炸鱼薯条
It was fish and chips.
你误解他了 萨姆不是坏人
Look, you got off on the wrong foot. Sam's not a bad guy.
这跟好人坏人没关系
It's not about bad or good.
他不尊重我
He doesn't respect me.
你们不是应该说 “没有 他很尊重你”吗
This is where you're supposed to say, "Yes, he does."
- 他很尊重你 - 太迟了
- He respects you. - Way too late.
这个从美国人民那里
Is a man who got 83 million votes
获得8300万张选票的人 得到的尊重难道还不够吗
from the American people not feeling properly respected?
明天见
See you tomorrow.
- 你看了演讲稿吗  - 看了 挺好的
- Did you look over your speech? - Yeah. It's solid.
只要稍加魅力 就能点燃群众的激情
I'll hit it with some fireworks. It'll crackle.
今天早上应该会很不错
It's gonna be a good morning.
没那么简单
Won't be that simple.
说吧
Tell me.
西班牙的行动失败了
Sideways op, Spain.
目标是谁
Who was the target?
维克托格拉多夫 俄罗斯军火商 现已成为极端分子
Viktor Gradov. Russian-born arms dealer turned extremist.
对 黑市武器开发商
Right. Black market weapons developer
几年前他搞到了浓缩钚
who got his hands on enriched plutonium a few years back.
于是我们搞垮了他的生意
Yeah, that's when we took him out of business.
在北约特遣部队的帮助下 摧毁了他的制造工厂
Destroyed his manufacturing plant with the help of a NATO task force.
我们发动了空袭 摧毁了他的整个设施
We launched an air strike, destroyed his whole facility.
在那之后格拉多夫就消失了
After that, Gradov went off the grid.
西班牙这次行动 是我们这两年首次有机会逮捕他
Spain was our first chance to move on Gradov in two years.
他现在人在哪
Where is he now?
不知道
In the wind.
国安局正在搜查边境入口和机场 想得到点消息
NSA is scraping border entries and airport screenings for noise.
情报和研究部没有机会做常规分析...
Intelligence and Research didn't have the chance to do their usual analysis.
该死 要我说多少次  绝不能漏过任何情报
Bloody hell. How many times I've got to say it? We do not leapfrog intel.
关于诺埃尔
About Noel,
- 如果你想聊聊... - 不想
- if you want to talk... - I don't.
我们应该提醒克拉克的团队 注意杰克戈登这个人
We should warn Clarke's team about Jack Gordon.
杰克喜欢问很尖锐的问题
Jack always goes for the jugular,
他肯定会揪着西班牙的事穷追猛打
and he will fry us over this Spain thing.
你跟总统的通讯主管说了
Did you tell the president's comms director
让他按剧本表演吗
that he must stick to the script?
说了
Yes.
很好 希望他别提无法满足的要求
Good. Hopefully he doesn't start writing checks that we can't cash.
他到现在都还分不清 新闻发布会和媒体宣传会的区别
He still hasn't figured out the difference between a press conference and a press junket.
首相先生
Mr. Prime Minister.
- 总统先生 - 你好
- Mr. President. - Yeah.
我们终于见面了
We finally meet.
很遗憾你错过了就职典礼
You know, it was a shame that you missed the inauguration.
真的非常精彩
It was a hell of a show.
- 那是肯定 - 好吧
- Sure it was. - Yeah.
这个...
Well...
我们走吧
Shall we?
等等
Uh, wait, wait.
我们应该好好享受这一刻 这是我们的首场二重唱
We should savor this moment. I mean, this is... it's our debut duet.
“二重唱”
Duet?
对 就好比我是德瑞博士 而你是阿姆
Yeah. It's like I'm Dr. Dre and you're Eminem,
这是我们第一次同台演出
and we're taking that stage for the first time together.
我是阿姆
I'm Eminem?
对了 关于西班牙的可怕情况
Listen, um, about this terrible situation in Spain.
如果有记者提问
If it comes up out there,
我们就避而不谈 把皮球踢给别人
I'd just steer clear of it. Let's just punt it.
-“踢给别人”  - 没错
- Punt it? - Yeah.
踢给谁
To where?
稍后来解决这事的人
Well, to later.
今天的重点是北约
Today's about NATO,
- 清洁能源 轻松愉快的话题 -“轻松愉快” 好吧
- clean energy, light and bright stuff. - Light and bright. Okay.
你想一起热热身吗
You want to warm up together?
- 做点呼吸练习  - 我这不是在呼吸吗
- Do some breathing exercises? - I'm already breathing.
- 收到 好吧... - 嗯
- Roger that. Well... - Yeah.
那就开始我们的表演吧
Let's dance, I guess.
嘿 就当帮我们俩一个忙
Hey, uh, just do us both a favor out there.
别让杰克戈登提问
No questions from Jack Gordon.
好伙计
My guy.
从今天起
And as of today,
得益于我们两国共同开发的
thanks to this revolutionary new technology
这项革命性新技术 我们已成为能源合作伙伴
developed by both of our great nations, we are now partners in energy.
球床反应堆 不仅是对清洁能源的投资
The pebble-bed reactor is not just an investment in clean energy.
也是对安全的投资
It's also an investment in security.
能源安全就是国家安全
Energy security is national security.
它也是对创造就业的投资
It is also an investment in job creation.
能提供很多工作机会
A whole lot of jobs.
我们不再需要与俄罗斯
And we no longer have to deal with the Russians,
沙特或委内瑞拉在石油问题上打交道
the Saudis or the Venezuelans on oil.
我们非常期待在接下来的几天内
But we are keen to present this global initiative
向我们的北约伙伴展示这一全球倡议
to our NATO partners in the coming days.
好了 问题时间
Okay. Questions?
德林杰总统
President Derringer!
《水蟒》刚刚宣布
Uh, it's just been announced that Water Cobra
将扩展为一个电影宇宙
is being expanded into a cinematic universe.
你会去客串吗
Any chance you'll be making a cameo?
各位 我答应过第一夫人 如果我再穿“单宁毒液”的装扮
Oh, folks. I promised the first lady if I ever dressed up as the Venom in Denim again,
那肯定是在椭圆办公室 或者是为了白宫记者晚宴
it'd either be in the Oval boudoir or for the White House Correspondents' Dinner,
你只能受邀参加晚宴 椭圆办公室可去不了
and you're only invited to the last one.
- 克拉克首相 - 请提问
- Prime Minister Clarke. - Yes?
《每日邮报》刊登了 公爵夫人和其新男友的照片
The Daily Mail have photos of the duchess and a new beau.
关于你前女友的最新动态 你有何评论
Any comments about your ex-girlfriend's latest escapades?
- 好吧 谁有真正的问题  - 等一下
- Okay. Who has a real question? - Hey, hold on a minute.
还有谁不想让首相继续打光棍了
Now, who else is tired of seeing the prime minister as a single man?
我们给他定制一季《单身汉》吧
I'll tell you what. How about we get him his own season of The Bachelor?
- 还有谁想加入  - 好啊 搞起来
- Who's with me? - Yeah! Let's do it!
杰克戈登
Jack Gordon.
今天早上在西班牙 有六名英国人和美国人死亡
There are six dead British and Americans in Spain this morning.
您能否就抓捕 著名军火商维克托格拉多夫的
Can you comment on speculation this is the result
秘密行动失败的猜测发表评论
of a failed covert operation to capture known arms dealer Viktor Gradov?
秘密行动之所以是秘密 是有原因的
Covert operations are covert for a reason.
其他的无可奉告
That's all I'm gonna say on that.
不仅如此 格拉多夫会后悔 昨天没有束手就擒
That and Gradov's gonna wish we caught him yesterday.
因为当我们抓到他的时候
Because when we do get our hands on him,
他就会知道复仇
he is going to be forming a special relationship
到底是什么滋味
with the concept of retribution.
我们还应将此 作为一个集体反思的时刻
We should also be using this as a collective moment of introspection,
找出哪里出了问题 并从中吸取教训
find out what went wrong and learn from it.
有消息称 行动期间访问了“梯队系统”
Leaks indicate that Echelon was accessed during the op.
你是否准备好承认 有这么一个秘密监视系统
Are you ready to acknowledge the existence of a top secret surveillance program
监控着我们所有的邮件 视频会议
which monitors all of our emails, video conferences,
- 还有电话... - 汤姆
- phone calls... - Tom.
我不能一直说“无可奉告”
There's only so many times I can say "no comment" to that.
所以我来回答
I'll comment.
我们的敌人应该感到害怕
Our enemies should be afraid.
我们有这样的工具和技术
We have the tools and we have the technology
如果他们胆敢进犯 我们就能找到并摧毁他们
to find and destroy them if they challenge us.
我们会做出以下承诺
We aren't making any promises except that
我们将不懈努力以取得成果
we will work tirelessly to get results.
没错
Well, we are.
美利坚合众国在此承诺 一定会取得成果
The United States of America is promising results.
德林杰总统 你有什么话要对
President Derringer,
在西班牙遇害者的家人们说吗
do you have a message for the families of the men and women killed in Spain?
我在特种部队待过很长时间
I've spent a lot of time with Special Forces.
和他们一起训练
Trained with them,
从他们身上学习
learned from them.
我要说的是 我们必须做得更好 我们也一定能做得更好
And what I have to say is we must do better. We will do better.
当你说“和他们一起训练” 是指为了电影角色训练吧
When you say, um, "trained with them," that was for an acting role, yes?
- 是的 但是... - 我是说 你从来没服过役
- Yes, but, uh... - I mean, y-you've never served.
作为一个在英国军队服役的人 你们都知道
As someone who did serve in the British Army, as most of you know,
如果我对家属有话要说
if I did have something to say to the families,
我会当面跟他们说 而不会通过你向英雄致敬 杰克
I would say it to them directly. I do not salute heroes through you, Jack.
说实话 你没上过战场
To be clear, you never saw combat.
恕我直言 先生们 你们是政客
But with all due respect, gentlemen, you're politicians.
你们不会真把自己当成真英雄了吧
You don't equate yourselves with actual heroes, do you?
真是糟透了
Well, that was a shit-bath.
社交媒体上热议不断 #指挥官之争 正登上热搜
Socials are lighting up. Hashtag "commanders in beef" is trending.
该死
Goddamn it!
你很清楚杰克戈登是个麻烦 我警告过你的
You knew Jack Gordon was trouble. I warned you.
我的地盘 我想让谁提问就让谁提问
My town. I'll call on whomever I want.
休息五分钟
Let's take five.
我可不怕媒体
You know, I'm not afraid of the press.
不是每个人都需要被所有人喜欢
Not all of us have a compulsive need to be liked by everyone.
恕我直言...
With all due respect...
我知道你乐于替他出头
I know you like to fight his battles for him, Simone.
你的总统任期才刚开始
Your presidency is in diapers.
你还在学习中
You're on a learning curve.
- 我干这行已经六年了 - 你 我能替自己出头
- I've been on this slog for six years. - You? I fight my own battles.
要不拿数据说话 要不先从
You, you want to talk numbers?
你的支持率开始说起
Your approval ratings, that's a great place to start.
不像你 我要的是结果 而不是别人在Ins上给我点赞
Unlike you, I'll take results over likes on Instagram.
你都不在乎别人怎么想 你还要求大家集体反思一下
You-you clearly don't care about what people think. You called for a collective moment of introspection?
这么说吧 我更关心 民众如何还得起抵押贷款
Let's just say I'm more concerned with how people pay their mortgages
如何送孩子上大学
and send their kids to university.
是啊 公众最爱看 政客们给他们布置“家庭作业”了
Oh, for sure, 'cause God knows there's nothing the public loves more than politicians giving them homework.
你是在为炸鱼薯条那事生气吗  如果是的话就直说吧
Is this about the fish and chips thing? 'Cause if it is, just say it.
我一点也没为这破事生气
I am not mad about the goddamn fish and chips thing.
够了 你们俩今天都表现得不怎么样
Enough. Neither of you were at your best today.
同意 我们得尽快解决这事
Agreed. We need to give this a short shelf life.
他说得对 改变说话方式
He's right. Change the narrative.
把这变成一个机会...
Turn this into an opportunity.
证明你们是团结的
To show that you guys are united.
我知道了
I've got it.
你们一起飞去得里雅斯特
You fly to Trieste together
搭乘空军一号
on Air Force One.
我不确定飞机坐不坐得下
I don't know if we have enough room.
不用 我不坐 感谢你的好意
No, I'm good, thank you very much.
- 而且我今晚必须去华沙 - 不 听我说完
- And besides, I have to be in Warsaw tonight. - Hear me out, all right?
你们俩在伦敦的飞机舷梯上停留35秒 挥手微笑
You both do 35 seconds on the airstairs here in London, waving and smiling,
在华沙短暂停留下 你们早餐前就能到达得里雅斯特
pit stop in Warsaw. You'll be in Trieste by breakfast.
到那时 你们在舷梯上的照片 那团结一致的景象
By that time, pictures of you on those airstairs, a vision of solidarity,
将会登上全球十份报纸中的八份头版
will be on the front page of eight out of ten newspapers all around the world.
昆西
Quincy.
布拉德肖
Bradshaw.
我是美国总统 我不和任何人共用舞台
I am the President of the United States. I don't share the stage with anyone.
搭便车 这就是你的解决方案
Hitch a ride? Is that your solution?
这样民意调查中的支持率 必将提升三个百分点
It's a guaranteed three-point bump in the polls.
听着 我们的任期刚开始
Look, we are in the early days.
你得证明你能交到朋友
You've got to show you can make friends.
眼下 我们更需要他 而非他需要我们
Right now we need him more than he needs us.
萨姆 为了胜利
Sam, take the win.
坐他的飞机吧
Take the flight.
你一起吗
Will you be there?
我跟先遣队一起
I'll go with the advance team.
昆西和我会确保 得里雅斯特的跑道边挤满媒体
Quincy and I will foam the runway with the press in Trieste.
首相先生
Mr. Prime Minister.
能否请你赏脸 和我一起乘坐空军一号
Would you do me the honor and fly with me aboard Air Force One?
说实话...
I'll be honest.
我整晚睡不着在想
It kept me up all night.
为什么我花重金 请来最顶尖的狙击手
How is it that I hire the best sniper money can buy
结果他偏偏在关键时刻失手了
and he misses the one shot meant to protect
没能护住我整个行动中最重要的人
the most important man in my entire operation?
好吧 谢谢 但我们都在尽自己的职责
Yeah, thanks, but we're all just doing our part.
都是拼图的碎片 被子上的补丁
Pieces of a puzzle, patches on a quilt...
我先以为是设备故障
I assumed it was faulty equipment.
现在我知道了 是人为失误
But now I know it was human error.
就像你说的...
Like you say...
“发生的一切都是最好的安排”
"Everything that happens happens for the best."
是啊
Yes.
来吧
Come.
坐
Sit down.
我妈妈很喜欢这句话
My mother was very fond of that phrase.
她是个格达尔卡 算命的
She was a gadalka. A fortune teller.
她会看茶叶
She read tea leaves.
她能看到未来
She could see the future.
她看到了我的未来 说有一天
She saw mine and said that one day
我会受到非常不公正的待遇
I would be served a great injustice,
我人生的目标 就是让那些责任人付出代价
and it would be my mission in life to punish those responsible.
没有任何事 任何人
And nothing or no one
能阻止我
would get in my way.
十多年来 美国总统首次...
It's been over a decade since a U.S. president
...在空军一号上接待英国首相
has hosted a British prime minister on Air Force One,
这次访问必将载入史册
making this trip one for the history books.
瞧瞧啊
Check her out.
刚下生产线
Fresh off the assembly line.
这款飞机的翼展 比前代型号宽了30英尺
30-foot wider wingspan than the previous model.
速度可以突破音速 转弯时像F-15战斗机一样灵活
Can break Mach 1, oh, and corners like an F-15.
很惊讶你没有在它侧面画火焰
Surprised you didn't paint flames on the side of it.
你这是在嫉妒 你的飞机很烂 而且名字也不酷
Ah, you're just jealous 'cause your plane sucks and doesn't have a cool name.
伙计们
Fellas.
我们爱威廉
We love Will! We love Will!
首相先生
Mr. Prime Minister.
我听说你喜欢黑麦威士忌
I heard you like rye.
这款酒来自我的家乡肯塔基
This one comes from my hometown in Kentucky.
这就是美国独特性与优越性的体现
Now, that is American exceptionalism in action.
谢谢
Thank you.
请慢用 先生
Enjoy, sir.
他在这呢 来这边
There he is. Come on.
跟克拉克首相打个招呼
Say hello to Prime Minister Clarke. Hey.
对他好点 他最喜欢哈里斯泰尔斯了
Be nice to him, Sawyer. He's besties with Harry Styles.
我不太确定 但如果他下次去华盛顿
Well, I don't know about that, but next time he's in Washington,
我看看能不能给你弄到个好座位
I'll see if I can get you some good seats.
- 谢谢 - 谢谢
- Thank you. - Thank you.
很高兴终于见到你 首相先生
Nice to finally meet you, Mr. Prime Minister.
不必 说实话 叫我萨姆就好
Now, honestly, just-just call me Sam.
很遗憾这次没能见面
I'm so sorry we missed each other.
你们俩照顾好自己 对他好一点 萨姆
You two take care of yourselves, and go easy on him, Sam.
我们还在学习
We're still learning the ropes.
- 我会尽量让他远离麻烦 - 好了 嘿
- I'll try and keep him out of trouble. - Okay, hey.
爱你们 明天再聊
Love you guys. Talk to you tomorrow.
你很擅长这个
You're good at that.
擅长什么
Good at what?
做正常人...
Being normal. Ish.
- 接近正常 - 我该说谢谢
Uh, thank you?
你应该更经常地 向人们展示你的这一面
You should show people that side of you more often.
第一步是结束单身
Start by ditching the bachelor status.
世界领导人如果未婚会让人不安
World leader who's unmarried?
留给人们太多想象空间
Freaks people out, leaves too much to the imagination.
他们会想象什么
What are they imagining?
我不确定 类似《大开眼戒》里那种派对
I don't know, Eyes Wide Shut parties
或者到了晚上你就成了蒙面义警 做一些奇怪的 令人不安的事
or by night you're some masked vigilante into some weird, unsettling shit.
听着 人们想要的是确切性
Look, people want clarity.
婚姻能提供一种确切性 能让你的形象显得更亲切
Marriage gives them clarity. It softens the image.
我搞糊涂了 你是在给我建议
I'm confused. Are you giving me advice
还是在向我推荐你的烂情景喜剧
or are you pitching me on one of your shit rom-coms?
我懂 你不喜欢我的电影
All right, I get it. You don't like my movies.
我从没看过你的电影
I've never seen your movies.
因为萨姆克拉克不喜欢娱乐
Because Sam Clarke is the man who does not like to be entertained.
不 是因为我喜欢真正的电影
No, it's 'cause I like actual cinema.
拜托 难道是我不想 和韦斯安德森或奉俊昊合作吗
Come on. You don't think I wanted to work with Wes Anderson or Bong Joon Ho?
我当然想
Of course I do.
我受过正统训练
I'm classically trained.
你知道我和爱德华诺顿演过戏吗
Did you know I once did a play with Edward Norton?
但老天爷一直说我拿枪会很帅
But the universe keeps telling me I look cool with a gun in my hand.
玩具枪
A toy gun.
你是怎么回事
What is it with you?
一天到晚觉得自己比别人都强
Walking around, thinking you're better than everybody else.
一开始我以为是英国人都这样 现在我明白了 只有你这样
First, thought it was a British thing. Then I realized it's a you thing.
我认识保罗麦卡特尼 好吗
I know Paul McCartney, okay?
他比你受欢迎多了
He's put a whole lot more wins on the board than you,
而且他酷毙了
and he is cool as shit!
- 要我送过去吗  - 我送就行 谢谢
- Want me to take it up? - I got it. Thanks.
你知道吗 我不会 因为想要被喜欢或被爱而道歉
And you know what? I'm not gonna apologize for wanting to be liked or loved.
我们很幸运 干着世上最非凡的两份工作
We're blessed with two of the most extraordinary jobs ever created,
这份工作的一部分 就是灌输希望 让人们感觉美好
and part of that job is to instill hope. It's to make people feel good.
但是根据我的经验 希望最终只会带来失望
Yeah, well, based on my experience, okay, hope is just delayed disappointment.
希望既填不饱肚子 也遮不了风雨
Doesn't put food on the table. Doesn't put a roof over anyone's head.
如果你只想着如何让人们感觉美好
And if you want to focus on making people "feel good,"
那你就永远无法理解如何帮助他们
then you're never gonna understand how to help them.
你是总司令 不是拉斯维加斯的DJ
You are the commander in chief. You're not some DJ in Vegas.
我的职位头衔用不着你提醒
I don't need to be refreshed on my job title.
我们把话说清楚
Let's be clear about that.
别告诉机长我偷了他的藏货给你们
Don't tell the captain I snuck you his stash.
多谢
Thanks.
前往拦截
Move to intercept.
要知道 等你的蜜月期结束
Just know, once this honeymoon period is over,
你的未来只会让你失望
there is only disappointment in your future,
因为这份工作 我的工作 就是受苦
because this job, my job, is about suffering.
是吗 预言家先生 等那天真来了 咱俩倒是可以坐下来
Yeah, Nostradamus? When that day comes, maybe then you and I can sit down
好好聊一聊炸鱼薯条
and talk about it over some fish and chips.
我就知道你迟早会说真话 果然如此
I knew the truth would come out. There it is.
真棒 你成功了 阿加莎克里斯蒂破案了
Oh, great. You did it, Agatha Christie. You cracked the case.
- 给大家奖励点史酷比饼干吧 - 威廉 翻篇吧
- Let's give Scooby Snacks to everybody. - Will, let it go.
你大白天在莱塞特广场正中央
You took my opponent for fish and chips in broad daylight
请我的竞争对手吃炸鱼薯条 你明知道那里全是摄影师
in the middle of "Liester" Square, and you knew photographers would be there!
是莱斯特广场
First of all, it's pronounced Leicester Square.
别闹了 他是老朋友 我只是带他去吃午饭
And, no, bollocks, he's an old friend. I took him for lunch.
你明知道这会引人遐想
You knew there were political implications.
又不是人人都能仰仗 议会中剑桥精英集团的政治资源
Not all of us have some posh Cambridge Mafia in Parliament
赢得选举
helping us get elected!
我拼了命才走到这里
I busted my ass to get to where I am.
我出生于政府公屋社区
I was born in a housing estate
从未享有任何特权资源
and was never given anything on a silver platter.
为了交剑桥的学费 我打了三份工 然后又去参军
I worked three jobs to pay for Cambridge,
然后开始社区组织工作 继而担任国防武官职务
and then to the Army, and then to community organizing,
我是一步步从议会基层爬上来的 懂吗 不是所有人搞政治
and then Defence Attaché, and worked my way up through Parliament. Now, not all of us got our political start
都靠经纪公司看上 你那副“大兵乔”的帅脸
because some commercial agent decided they like our G.I. Joe jawline!
注意你的语言
Watch it!
你从内裤模特混到走红毯
No, no, no! You went from modeling your underwear to being on the red carpet
一直到摸到核按钮
to having your finger on the nuclear button,
连一天基层都没干过
all without doing a single day of public service!
说真的 伙计 看到你在这扮总统
So, yes, mate, when I see you play the role of president,
我恶心得都要吐了 你就会念台词
it makes me sick to my stomach, because you know your lines--
你可太会了
oh, yes, you do--
但总统这个角色你可演不来
but you're not believable in the part.
我要是能给你对手站台 早站了
And if I could've endorsed your opponent, yes, I would've,
至少这样白宫里会有一个真领袖
because at least there'd be a real leader in the White House
而不是个丢人现眼 只会爆米花政治的戏精总统
and not some embarrassing, bullshit, popcorn president!
- 什么  - 你听到我说的了
- What's that? - You heard what I said!
不是 那是什么
No, what's that?
先生们 待在办公室 保证自己安全
Sirs, secure yourselves in the office. Fasten your seatbelts.
系好安全带 先生 请坐下
Sir. Take your seat, please.
发生什么了
What's happening?
不明航空器 你已进入限制空域
Unidentified aircraft, you're in restricted airspace.
立即转向撤离 否则将遭火力拦截
Pull away immediately or you will be fired upon.
全频段无线电失效
All radios are out.
所有通讯全部中断
Comms are fried across the board.
天啊
Dear God.
- 准备武器 - 是 长官
- Ready the weapons. - Yes, sir.
大事不妙
Oh, shit.
先生们
Uh, gentlemen.
被多枚武器锁定
Multiple inbound bogies!
开火
Open fire!
总统先生 先生
Mr. President! Sir!
这是怎么回事
What the hell's going on?
该死
Shit.
我们得去飞机后部 快走
We got to get to the back of the plane! Go! Go! Go!
别再射无人机了
Stop shooting the drones!
快射飞机
Shoot the goddamn plane!
抓紧了
Hold on!
紧急下降至10000英尺 以稳定舱内压力
Initiating emergency descent to 10,000 for cabin pressure stabilization.
走 后面有降落伞
Let's go! There are parachutes in the back!
又来了一波
Here comes another wave.
二号引擎失灵
We lost engine two.
准备压杆操作
Gonna lean into it.
快 我们得跳过去
Come on, we got to jump!
那边 穿过门
That way! Through the door!
快 先生 快走
Come on, sir! Move!
正在改平
We're leveling out.
他们完蛋了
They're finished.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
走
Let's go!
快点 快走 快
Come on! Let's move! Quick!
这两个应该能用
These two should be intact.
该死 我们要落在白俄罗斯领空
Shit! We're going down in Belarusian airspace.
你们得去我们在波兰的安全屋
You'll need to get to our safe house in Poland.
跳出去后使劲拉手柄 剩下的就交给降落伞
Rip it hard once you're out. The chute'll do the rest.
你跟我用一个伞
We can double up.
不行 太冒险了
Not a chance. Too risky.
那这些人怎么办
What about all these people?
我们都有自己的职责
We all have our jobs to do.
你们的职责就是活下去
Yours is to survive.
去华沙格达通斯克大桥下面的 金山矿业公司
Get to Golden Mountain Mining Company under the Gdanski Bridge in Warsaw.
先生们 重复一遍
Let me hear it, sirs.
金山矿业公司
Golden Mountain Mining Company.
格达通斯克大桥
Gdanski Bridge!
我很荣幸 总统先生
It's been an honor, Mr. President.
该死
Oh, shit.
我们刚刚收到一段令人震惊的影像
We have just received devastating footage
显示空军一号在白俄罗斯西部坠毁
of Air Force One going down over Western Belarus.
威廉姆德林杰总统 和萨缪尔克拉克首相
President William Derringer and Prime Minister Samuel Clarke...
据推测已遇难
are presumed dead.
我们正等待五角大楼 就事故潜在原因或嫌疑人发表声明
We're awaiting word from the Pentagon on the potential cause or suspects.
目前尚无组织宣称 对这起悲剧性事件负责
No groups are claiming responsibility for this tragic loss.
议会正召开紧急会议商讨继任方案
An emergency session of Parliament is convening to discuss succession strategy,
片刻前 伊丽莎白科克副总统
while moments ago V.P. Elizabeth Kirk was sworn in
在意大利得里雅斯特 宣誓就任代理总统
as acting president in Trieste, Italy.
当地聚集的北约领导人正表达哀悼
...where gathering NATO leaders are offering their condolences
与坚定支持
and unyielding solidarity.
这场本该是北大西洋联盟的庆典
What was meant to be a celebration of the North Atlantic Alliance
此刻被前所未有的震惊与哀悼淹没
is now a time of unprecedented shock and mourning.
妈呀
Oh, geez.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好 你呢
Yeah. You?
他们怎么上我的飞机的
How the hell'd they get on my plane?
肯定是有内奸帮忙
With the help of someone on the inside, that's for sure.
波兰边境要往那边走24公里
The Polish border is about 15 miles that way.
步行的话我们明早就能到安全屋了
On foot, we can be at that safe house by morning.
不用 救援马上就到
No. The cavalry's coming.
不会有救援的 伙计
Cavalry's not coming, mate.
白俄罗斯会控制坠机现场
Belarus will want to control the crash site.
他们不会让任何飞机进入领空的
Won't be letting any planes into their airspace,
我们的人不可能为了捡尸体 偷偷穿越敌军防线
and there's no way our guys are sneaking across enemy lines to retrieve corpses.
他们只能当无人生还
They have to assume there are no survivors.
该死
Shit.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
给我妻子打电话 我要让她知道我还活着
Calling my wife. I'm letting her know I'm alive.
不行 不能打电话 好吗
No. No, no, no, no. No. No phones. All right?
- 照我说的做 - 什么
Do as I do.
我们刚经历了史上最严重的安全漏洞
We just survived the worst security breach in history,
所以你必须假设 想要你命的人
so you have to assume whoever wants you dead
正在监听通讯
is listening to communications, okay?
我得让我的家人知道我没事
I'm calling my family to let them know I'm okay.
我们得让全世界知道我们没事
And we should let the world know we're okay.
瞧瞧吧 我们哪没事了
We're not okay.
听好了 如果我们落入敌手 最好的情况是
All right? If we fall into the wrong hands,
被当作政治筹码踢来踢去
they use us as a political football.
最坏的情况是他们会杀鸡儆猴
Worst-case scenario is... they make an example of us.
把手机放下
Now put that down!
知道上一个向在职总统扔鞋的人 是什么下场吗
You know what happened to the last guy who threw a shoe at a sitting president?
是挂得挺“直”的
You're not sitting. You're hanging. All right?
听好了 滚开
You know what? Piss off.
- 你想让我滚开  - 是的
- You want me to piss off? - Yeah.
好吧 我滚
Okay, I'll piss off.
我一路滚到华沙
I'll piss off all the way to Warsaw.
你自己在鸟类保护区欢度余生吧
Enjoy living the rest of your life as a bird sanctuary.
好吧 别滚
All right, don't piss off.
拜托 帮我下来好吗
Would you just help me down for Chrissakes, please?
好吧 瞧瞧
There you go. Look at that.
一个美国动作片英雄还得我帮忙
An American action hero asking me for help.
手上做着最高尚的事 嘴巴还是这么小气刻薄
Even in his most noble moments, he was still petty and mean-spirited.
我数到三就放你下去
I'm gonna drop you on three.
三
Three!
- 你还好吧 德林杰  - 我还好
- You all right back there, Derringer? - I'm fine.
- 听见好重的喘气声跟呼哧声 - 我没呼哧 好吗
- Hearing a lot of panting and snuffling. - I don't snuffle, okay?
再说了 少操心别人怎么喘气
Besides, don't concern yourself with how another man breathes.
有点边界感 伙计
Boundaries, guy.
没什么好不好意思的
Nothing to be embarrassed about.
你这样的人本来就没什么毅力
Endurance is tough for guys like you.
- 我这样的人  - 对 你这样的人 健身房强者
- Guys like me? - Guys like you. You know, gym strong.
-“健身房强者”  - 健身房强者
- Gym strong? - Gym strong.
而不是
As opposed to?
真正的强者
Strong strong.
你想看看健身房强者的本事吗
Want to see gym strong?
我要把树从地上拔出来抡死你
I'll rip a tree out of the ground and beat you to death with it, huh?
快动手吧
Go on, then.
什么
What?
把那棵树从地上拔出来抡死我
Rip that tree out and beat me to death with it.
我就知道
That's what I thought.
别再说蠢话了
Silly thing to say, really.
谁让你选最粗的树了
Picked the biggest tree.
我的天啊
Dear God.
我觉得应该没人能活下来
Think he's had the day off.
这是谁干的
Who the hell did this?
我们有很多敌人
We got a lot of enemies.
但现在我们的任务是活着回去
Right now we got to get home alive. That's our job.
错 真正的任务是揪出幕后黑手 让他们血债血偿
No, our real job is to find out who did this and make them pay.
我和你一样想抓住他们 但这不是一朝一夕的事
Look, I want to get them just as much as you do, but these things don't happen overnight.
我们得找准时刻 我们花了十年时间 发起两次战争
We got to pick our moment. Took us ten years and two wars
- 才抓到本拉登 - 我不会再等十年了
- before we got bin Laden. - I'm not waiting ten years.
有一件事是肯定的 做出这事的人很有胆量
One thing for certain, whoever did this got some big balls.
我认为这绝对只是个开头
There's no reason to think this wasn't just phase one.
告诉五角大楼提高防御状态
Tell the Pentagon to move DEFCON status up,
并告知俄罗斯 中国和伊朗 此刻不要有任何冒险的举动
and inform Russia, China and Iran this is not a moment to get adventurous.
别挑战我们 别以为我们分心了
Don't challenge us and don't think we're distracted.
什么事
Yes?
“梯队”正在等待系统安全更新
Echelon is standing by for system security update.
拜托了
Please.
我是科克
This is Kirk.
我是梯队总监亚当斯
This is Echelon Director Adams.
请确认声纹 并扫描视网膜
Please confirm voiceprint and retinal scan.
“阿尔法 回声 布拉沃 阿尔法 查理 祖鲁 探戈”
Alpha, Echo, Bravo, Alpha, Charlie, Zulu, Tango.
声纹已确认
Voiceprint confirmed.
生物识别认证通过
Biometrics confirmed.
启动政府延续预案
Commence continuity of government protocol.
先生
Sir.
发生什么事了
What's happening?
他们在重启系统
They're rebooting the system.
倒计时三 二 一
In three, two, one.
快了
Almost there.
有人入侵了系统
Someone's inside the system.
发生什么了
Uh, wh-what's happening?
我们已经取得了“梯队”的控制权
We are now in control of Echelon.
这才像话嘛 我们去华沙的车有了
Now we're talking. There's our ride to Warsaw.
我们不能就这么走过去 让他们载我们一程
We can't just walk down and ask them for a lift.
我同意 但你错了 我们可以
I'd agree with you, but you're wrong. We can.
我们可是地球上最出名的两个人
We're two of the most recognizable men on the planet.
你连最出名的英国人都算不上
Ha. You're not even one of the most recognizable British people.
- 你懂我意思 - 重点是我们需要帮助
- You get my point. - The point is we need help,
所以我们就找他们求助
we ask them for help.
你不明白“保持低调”的意思吗
What part of "keep our heads down" don't you understand?
- 你有更好的主意  - 当然 我建议动作快点
- You got a better idea? - Yeah, I do. I say we move fast,
沿着树林边摸过去 去把那辆车偷了
creep along that tree line and hot-wire that car over there.
- 你什么时候学会偷车了  - 我不会 但你会
- Since when do you know how to hot-wire? - I don't, but you do.
你16岁因为偷了邻居的科迈罗被抓过
You got busted at 16 for stealing your neighbor's Camaro.
- 你从哪听说的  - 我查过你了
- Where'd you hear about that? - I vetted you.
你查过我了
You vetted me?
我是美国总统 应该是我查你
I'm the President of the United States. You don't vet me. I vet you.
那你查我了吗
Well, did you vet me?
这不是重点
Not the point.
加油
Come on. Come on.
耶 搞定
Yeah, there he is.
兄弟们
Boys.
噢 不好
Oh, no.
他们过来了
We have incoming.
我去跟他们聊聊 他们会载我们一程的
I'm going to talk to them. They'll give us a ride.
不不不 赶紧把车启动 我们离开这里
No, no, no. You're gonna start this car, and we're gonna get out of here.
信我 我跟喝啤酒的小伙子很合得来
Trust me. I poll really well with young men who drink beer.
我跟他们有共同语言
I speak their language.
你跟他们有共同语言才怪了
Except you literally don't speak their language.
电影就是国际语言
Cinema is the international language.
- 看我展现魅力 - 威廉 嘿
- Watch the magic. - Will. Hey.
嘿 伙计们 你们好吗
Hey, fellas, how's it going?
我们迷路了 你们能帮帮忙吗
We got a little turned around. We could use some help.
是我啊 威廉德林杰
It's me, Will Derringer.
你们肯定知道
You know, Water Cobra.
《水蟒》
怎么没反应
Huh, still nothing?
手表不错
Nice watch.
我觉得你应该把手表给他
I think you should give him the watch.
给我戴着试下
Let me try it on.
这是基努在《大屠杀2》杀青时 送我的礼物
This is a gift from Keanu when we wrapped Carnage 2.
好吧 希望基努还送过你功夫课
Yeah, well, I hope Keanu gifted you some kung fu lessons,
因为我们马上就要挨揍了
'cause we're about to get our asses kicked.
伙计 你搞错情况了
Man, read the room.
这下明白了
See?
够了
That's enough!
你右边
On your right!
对不起
Oh, sorry.
别出手
Don't.
住手
Stop!
我说住手
I said, stop!
你做了什么
What have you done?
你们死定了
You are dead men.
嘿
Hey!
你还好吗
Ah, God. You okay?
赶紧滚回家
Get your asses home!
你们这群蠢蛋
You half-witted cretins!
美国人
Yankees?
不不不 加拿大人
No, no, no. Canadians.
为什么要说是加拿大人  人人都爱美国人
Why'd you say Canadians? Everybody loves Americans.
只有美国人爱美国人 我们是加拿大人 相信我
Americans love Americans. Today we're Canadians. Trust me.
你们要去哪里
Where you go?
越过边境去华沙
Across the border to Warsaw.
文件呢
Papers?
没有文件
No papers.
好吧
Okay.
我带你们去
I take you.
我的车超棒
I have great ride.
这经历写进回忆录肯定很赞
Eh, it'll be great for our memoirs.
“第14章 就像丘吉尔第一次会见
"Chapter 14. It was exactly like when Churchill met FDR for the first time,
罗斯福时一样 不过混着一点羊屎味”
just with an added splash of sheep shit."
情况本来可能会更糟
Could be worse.
还好有好心陌生人搭救
We're experiencing the kindness of a stranger.
现在我们能去安全的地方了
We're en route to safety.
等我们安全了 我们就要让敌人感受到愤怒的巨浪
Shortly after we get there, we'll make our enemies feel the ripple of our wrath.
- 那是不是... - 过去十年中最具开创性的
- Is-is that the... - Battle cry of the central character
动作片系列之一的 核心人物的战斗呐喊 当然
in one of the most seminal action franchises in the last decade? Hell yeah.
怎么了
What?
你们英国人的口号难道喊得很好吗
What do you Brits know about slogans anyway?
“保持冷静 继续生活”
"Keep calm and carry on."
你们知道吗
You know, that-that's actually like saying,
这跟说“什么都别做 以后也别做” 有什么区别
"Do nothing and continue to do nothing," right?
是啊 我们对口号的 崇拜程度可不一样
Yeah, we don't all fetishize taglines to the same degree.
- 是吗  - 对
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
好吧 这就是我不明白的点 好吗
Well, here's what I don't get, okay?
既然觉得人生是走不出的失败死循环
If life is such a M?bius strip of failure and futility,
那你为什么还要领导一个国家
why would you want to lead an entire nation?
我喜欢坐在发霉的旧房间里
I just like sitting in musty old rooms,
和无聊的老男人们争论税法
arguing with boring old men about tax code.
- 行吗  - 真好笑
- Okay? - That's a good one.
说真的
Seriously.
你为什么要竞选国家最高领导人
Why would you want to run for highest office in the land?
好吧 我先说
Yeah, fine. Me first.
你知道我28岁才第一次出国旅行吗
Did you know I didn't travel outside the U.S. until I was 28 years old?
是《水蟒》的第一次媒体巡演
First Water Cobra press tour.
那次我意识到每个国家的人都很棒
And it was there I realized, man, there are awesome people everywhere.
但这个世界却太支离破碎了
But the world is so damn fractured.
所以我想如果能用我的名人效应 做出哪怕一点点改变
So I figured if I could use my celebrity, even just for a little bit,
让人们团结起来 这不是件好事吗
to bring people together, wouldn't that be a good thing?
好吧 你的理由是什么
Okay. What's your excuse?
绝对不是因为相信自己 能让人们过上更好的生活
Certainly not about believing you'd deliver people to better days.
我相信会有更好的生活
I believe in better days.
说真的 今天比任何时候 都让我相信会有更好的生活
In fact, this day has got me believing in better days more than any other day,
因为哪一天都比
because any day would be better
跟你和一群羊困在这里强...
than being stuck in the muck with you and a bunch of...
你觉得今天很糟糕
You having a rough one, huh?
- 是的 - 是吗
- Yeah. - Yeah?
跟你的安保人员比呢
Take it up with your security detail.
或者跟我的安保比比
Or my security detail.
或者跟那架飞机上的任何人比比
Or anybody on that flight.
趴下
Down, down, down, down, down.
牲畜的护照和文件出示一下
Passports and documents for the livestock.
关掉引擎 下车
Kill the engine and get out.
你想做个交易吗
Maybe we could make a deal?
什么交易
What?
我想好回忆录怎么写了
Think I'm ready to write those memoirs now.
谢谢
Thank you.
给你
Take this.
我很荣幸
It was my pleasure...
总统先生
Mr. President.
祝你们好运
Good luck to both of you.
先生 “梯队”截获了华沙中情局 安全屋的监控录像
Sir, Echelon intercepted security footage from a CIA safe house in Warsaw
有两个人刚刚进去了
that just buzzed in two guests.
恕我直言
With all due respect,
我们击落空军一号时 已经拿到了需要的东西
we got what we needed when we took down Air Force One.
闭嘴
Quiet your mouth.
我们的行动很隐蔽 就算他们活着又能怎么样
And we kept our footprint tight, so who cares if they live?
我说要他们死 他们就得死
They die because I say they die.
他们还活着 在华沙
They're alive. Warsaw.
华沙 出发
Warsaw! Let's go!
你还活着
You're alive.
嘿 你因为我哭了
Okay. Hey. Are you crying because of me?
是啊 当然 伙计
Hell yeah, I am, man.
我是说 先生
I mean, sir.
对不起 我是马蒂科米尔
I'm sorry. Marty Comer.
好吧...
Oh, well.
基站探员 超级粉丝
Station agent. A huge fan.
还是个爱国者
Patriot.
我是英国首相萨姆克拉克 我们能进去吗
Sam Clarke, British prime minister. Can we come in?
可以
Yeah.
当然可以
Yeah, of course, of course.
那我们进去了
Like, now?
- 好的 请进 - 谢谢
- Yeah, now. - Thank you.
这边
Right this way.
好吧 我知道这听起来很疯狂
Okay, so I know this sounds, uh, bonkers,
- 但... - 有预案吗
- but... - What's the playbook on this?
这事的预案
For this?
哪有这种预案啊 我是说
Th-There is no damn playbook.
我们预案多得很 有针对极移的预案
I mean-- And we got lots of playbooks. Ones that account for pole shifts,
针对电脑有自我意识 太空猴子袭击
computers becoming self-aware, space monkey attacks,
各种乱七八糟的预案
all kinds of hectic shit.
但就是没有全世界目睹你们死亡
But, uh, none that contemplate you two sauntering in here
然后又大摇大摆出现的预案
after dying in front of the entire planet's eyes.
所以没有预案
So no playbook?
现做一个吧
Let's make one.
世人总说“英雄注定令人失望” 但请容我反驳
They say never meet your heroes, but to them I say:
他们显然从未见识过 威廉姆马修德林杰总统的非凡魅力
You've never met President William Matthew Derringer.
你名字首字母缩写 意思是大规模杀伤性武器
Your initials are WMD?
是啊 很讨厌 对吧
Yeah. Pretty bitchin', right?
跟我来 先生们
Follow me, gentlemen.
顺便说一句 你们来得正好
Your timing's great, by the way.
大使刚刚紧急把 所有在境人员召回了使馆
The ambassador just recalled all in-country personnel to the embassy.
外面的世界情况很糟糕
It's a real nut punch in a Ziploc bag out there.
要我说这些也不是巧合
And it ain't exactly a coincidence, if you ask me.
等等 什么不是巧合
W-Wait, what's not?
首先是你俩坠机
Well, first you two go down,
然后在北约会议现场 有人突然投下一枚“政治手雷”
and then someone rolls a political grenade into that NATO conference.
你们没听说吗
You guys didn't hear?
没有 我们今天有点忙
No, we've had a pretty busy day.
显然 “梯队”服务器被渗透了
Well, apparently, Echelon servers were infiltrated.
两小时前 一批机密文件被泄露
Two hours ago, a tranche of classified documents were leaked,
揭露了北约成员国数十年的秘密行动
exposing decades of covert activity amongst NATO members:
工业间谍 经济破坏 干预外国选举
industrial espionage, economic sabotage and the influencing of foreign elections.
最令人愤慨的是 这些行径并非针对敌对国家
And the real pisser? These weren't acts committed against enemy nations
而是针对彼此 是盟友间的相互倾轧
but against each other. These were friends against friends.
这简直是《老友记》第二季里 莫妮卡和瑞秋那种级别的塑料姐妹情
I'm talking some real Monica and Rachel season two shit.
明天的峰会将会是 电话亭中的困兽之斗
I mean, tomorrow's summit's gonna be a monkey knife fight in a telephone booth.
德国刚发现法国安插记者
Germany just found out France embedded journalists
干预其大选
to influence their last election.
捷克要求将意大利逐出北约
The Czech Republic wants Italy kicked out of the building
因为意大利蓄意破坏他们的经济
for trying to tank their economy.
而此刻我们却被挡在 全球最强的监控系统门外
All while we're locked out of the most powerful surveillance tool on this planet.
泄露了多少档案
How many files are we talking about?
两万 数量还在增加
20,000 and counting.
这是史上最具破坏性的国家机密泄露
It's the most damaging leak of state secrets in history.
有人在利用“梯队” 破坏北约组织的结构
Someone is using Echelon to tear at the very fabric of NATO.
北约一直在破坏自己的组织结构
Sounds like NATO has been tearing at the fabric of itself.
我打赌你很想说:“我早这么说过了”
Bet you're dying to say "I told you so."
- 你说什么  - 你当初是喊着“美国优先”赢的初选
- Excuse me? - You ran your primaries on "America first."
西蒙 我允许你来这里 是出于对威廉的尊重
Simone, I am allowing you to be in this room out of respect for Will.
允许我
Allowing me?
但请不要暗示 我对这个联盟有所保留
But please don't ever insinuate that I'm not all in on this alliance.
如果北约垮台 就再无针对专制独裁者的屏障了
If NATO falls, there's no more backstop against despots and dictators.
他们将不受任何制约
They run unchecked.
这可能会引发一系列事件
It could set off a series of events that-that would
破坏欧洲和世界其他地区的稳定
destabilize Europe and the rest of the world.
我们正在讨论的是 全球范围内冲突升级 秩序崩坏
We are talking about the potential for increased conflict, chaos
乃至真实战争威胁的可能性
and the very real threat of war on a global scale.
我们得出面证明自己还活着
We put our heads above water.
打给大使馆 通知他们我们在这里
Call the embassy. Let them know you have us.
不行 我们得假设 所有高官都已被渗透
No, we have to assume all high command posts are compromised.
胡说
Bullshit.
我们在一个安全的美国设施里
We are in a secure U.S. facility.
想尝尝品客薯片不
You guys want a hit of these Pringles?
上次我在安全的美国设施里时 我们被从四万英尺高空击落
Last time I was in one of those, we got shot out of the sky at 40,000 feet.
打电话
Make the call.
不许打电话
Don't make the call.
打电话
Make the call.
不许打电话
Don't make the call.
这电话我打不了
I can't make the call.
我是总司令 打电话
I'm the commander in chief! Make the goddamn call.
线路断了
The line's dead.
这正常吗
Is that normal?
不正常
No.
有些人是真想让我们死啊
Somebody really wants us dead.
我们在安全屋里很安全 对吧
We're safe, we're in a safe house, right?
我们能搞定的
We got this.
这些能给你们安全感吗
That feel safe enough for you?
- 该死 - 这可不是演电影 小伙子
- Shit. - Not in the movies now, son.
好了 听好
Okay, listen up.
我会带你们离开 但万一情况不妙
I'm gonna get you guys out of here, but just in case things do go south,
从第二出口撤退
best to beat a retreat through the secondary exit.
从这里出去左转 穿过大厅再左转 有个宿舍房间
That's a left out of here, down the hall, make a left. That's the bunk room.
右手边墙上有张海报
Another right, you should see a poster on the wall.
冲着海报打一拳就能顺利撤离了
You punch through that poster, you should be good to go.
帮我把电缆拉好 伙计们
Feed me, boys.
萨沙 萨沙
全都给我进来 快
All of you in here! Now!
这小子真疯啊
That boy's a nutter.
也许吧
Maybe,
我们大美国的疯子
but he's America's nutter.
走
Let's move.
快走
Get out of here.
Go!
快走
Come on!
不对 这边 他说右转
No, no, this way. He said right!
该死
Damn it!
别修了 约翰兰博 快走
No, no, Rambo! Come on!
找到海报了
Oh, found the poster.
打一拳
Punch it.
该死
Oh, goddamn it.
- 有什么问题  - 我做不到
- What's the problem? - I can't.
你是在搞笑吗 赶紧的啊
You having a laugh?! Come on!
原谅我
Forgive me.
我觉得我好像把那家伙干掉了
I think I killed that guy.
你干掉的只有那面墙
Only thing you killed is the wall.
不过我不得不说
I have to say, though,
你拿枪的样子确实挺酷
you do look good with a gun in your hand.
- 你先出去 - 不 你先出去
- You should go. - No, you go.
放下枪
Drop your guns!
抓到他们了
We have them.
收到
Coming down.
诺埃尔
Noel?
萨姆
Sam?
我以为你死了
- I thought you were dead. - I thought you were dead.
你怎么会没死呢
How are you not dead?
你们俩认识
You two know each other?
- 我们... - 我们以前是同事
- We... - We worked together. Back in the day.
你怎么找到我们的
How'd you find us?
不要
好吧 我告诉你
All right, I'll tell you!
说来话长
Long story.
嘿 你的后援呢
Hey, where's your backup?
没有后援
There is no backup.
我从西班牙就开始跟踪格拉多夫了
I've been trailing Gradov since Spain.
- 维克托格拉多夫是幕后黑手  - 那个军火贩子
- Victor Gradov is behind this? - The gun guy?
你是说 这一切都是 为了报复我们阻止他制造核武器
So you're saying this is all payback because we stopped him building nukes?
那边走
That way.
格拉多夫没有造核弹
Gradov wasn't building a nuke.
但他是个军火商啊
But he was a weapons developer.
他是 但他的儿子不是
He was, but his son wasn't.
- 他儿子跟这有什么关系  - 他儿子是个科学家
- Yeah, what's his son got to do with it? - His son was a scientist.
他非常聪明 取得了令人难以置信的突破
He was brilliant and made incredible breakthroughs.
他本来马上就能造出
He was on the brink of onlining
全球第一个“免堆芯融毁”核反应堆
the first ever nuclear reactor incapable of melting down.
球床反应堆技术
The pebble-bed technology.
我们那个球床反应堆技术
Our pebble-bed technology?
我们告诉全世界是我们研发的那个
The same technology I just told the world that we developed?
其实是格拉多夫的儿子发明的
You're telling me Gradov's son invented it?
他差一点就成功了
He was close.
当时他还需要一些浓缩钚
He still needed the enriched plutonium,
他父亲从黑市给他买了一批
which his father procured from the black market.
这笔交易被“梯队”监测到了
Echelon picked up on that transaction.
理所当然 我们以为他们要造核武器
Of course we assumed it was to build a weapon.
所以我们做了面对核威胁时该做的事
So we did what one does when faced with a nuclear threat.
我们朝额头扔弹头了
You dropped warheads on foreheads?
没错
We did.
死者中就有格拉多夫的儿子
Gradov's son was amongst the dead.
那次行动是北约批准的
The operation was sanctioned by NATO.
我们承担不起他制造核弹的风险
We couldn't risk the chance that he was building a nuke.
那会危机数百万人的生命
Millions of lives were at stake.
事后我们才发现他造的到底是什么
It was only in the aftermath we realized what was actually being developed.
于是在“梯队”的帮助下 我们得到了球床反应堆技术的图纸
So with the help of Echelon, we procured the schematics for the pebble-bed tech.
躲起来
Get back.
所以我们夺走了 他儿子的性命和遗产
So we took his son's life and then his legacy, huh?
还打算为此在得里雅斯特大肆庆祝
Which we were about to take a big victory lap for in Trieste.
恕我直言 但好像我们才是反派啊
Correct me if I'm doing the math wrong, but we're the assholes here.
听着 格拉多夫的儿子 不是因我们而死
Okay, look. Gradov's son didn't die because of us.
他死是因为他是魔鬼的儿子
He died because he's the son of the devil.
继续走
Let's keep it moving.
没有最高级别安全 格拉多夫是不可能做到的
Gradov couldn't have done all this without top-level security clearance.
问题是格拉多夫的内奸到底是谁
Okay, so then the question is: Who was Gradov working with on the inside?
得从那个安排我们登机的人开始查起
Got to start with the guy who put us both in that plane.
什么
What?
你本不该和我一起飞的
You weren't supposed to fly with me.
有人刻意向你灌输这个念头 并持续强化它
Somebody put that idea in your head, insisted on it.
昆西
Quincy.
华沙一处安全屋遭到袭击
A safe house was hit in Warsaw.
你觉得是怎么回事
What are you thinking?
可能是威廉和萨姆吗
Could be Will and Sam?
一定有什么值得追查的
There must have been something in there worth going after.
- 我们必须考虑这种可能性... - 难道你看到的和我们不一样
- We have to consider the possibility... - Did you not see what we all saw?
他们和空军一号一起坠毁了
They went down with Air Force One.
我不会放弃希望的 至少目前不会
I'm not giving up hope. Not yet.
我们都不该放弃
None of us should be.
我们必须集中精力 处理这次“梯队”泄密事件
We need to focus all our energies on this Echelon leak.
舆论愈演愈烈
The rhetoric is heating up.
但如果威廉和萨姆可能还活着...
But if there's even a chance that Will and Sam are still alive...
我们让中情局负责调查华沙的安全屋 而在这栋大楼里
We put CIA on the safe house in Warsaw. And right here in this building,
重点是和北约一起控制事态恶化
the focus is on stopping the bleeding with NATO.
我想尽快与 意大利 德国和法国会面
I want an audience with Italy, Germany and France as soon as possible.
让这些家伙们别再惺惺作态
It's time these guys stopped clutching their pearls
赶紧开始履行领导职责
and get on with the business of leading.
是我儿子 见谅
It's my son. Excuse me.
嗨 亲爱的
Hi, sweetheart.
西蒙 我知道威廉对你有多重要
Simone, I appreciate how much Will meant to you.
我知道他像你亲兄弟一样 但他已经死了
I know he was like a brother, but he's gone.
他们都死了
They're both gone.
你得开始接受这个现实
You need to start wrapping your head around that.
不可能是昆西
There's no way it's Quincy.
你怎么能确定
How can you be sure?
他是我的幕僚长 大学时代就相识的老搭档
He's been my chief of staff for six years. I known him since university.
是普通人眼里的他 还是你认知中的他
The way normal people know him or the way you know people?
又开始了
Ah, don't start that shit again.
他喜欢香肠薯泥还是炸鱼薯条
Does he like bangers and mash or fish and chips?
我知道你想干嘛
Ah, I see what you did there.
又想开始讨论炸鱼薯条的事
Sneaking the fish and chips back into the conversation.
为了这事你可真是绞尽脑汁啊
You must be exhausted trying to figure that out.
别互相挑来挑去 我们需要保持统一口味
Stop chipping away at each other. We need to be on the same page.
- 她是在用双关讽刺我们  - 她喜欢双关
- Did she just hit us with a pun? - She loves a pun.
我告诉过她 双关只适合心思简单的人
I tried to tell her puns are for simple people.
可我喜欢双关啊
I love puns.
- 说的就是你 - 各位
- My point exactly. - Guys!
这边
Over here.
快过来
Come on.
听着 现在关键是去得里雅斯特
Look, right now the key is getting to Trieste.
得里雅斯特
Trieste?
美国大使馆离这里有多远  他们能帮忙
How far away is the U.S. embassy from here? They can help us.
我们不去大使馆
We're not going to the embassy.
等等 你们怎么都不让我去大使馆
Wait, why won't anyone let me go to my embassy?
为什么大家突然都反对大使馆了
What does everybody suddenly have against embassies?
我们得假定所有高官都已被渗透
We have to presume that all high command posts are compromised.
你再说一遍我会尖叫的
Say that again, I'm gonna scream.
不是普通尖叫 而是喉底迸发的哀嚎
Not just a conventional scream, a guttural wail.
我们走
Let's go.
听着 我才是总司令
Listen, I'm the commander in chief.
好吧 恕我直言先生 你不是
Okay, respectfully, sir, no, you're not.
副总统几小时前已宣誓就职
The vice president was sworn in a few hours ago.
至于他 他从来都不是总司令
And he has never been commander in chief of anything.
国王才是
The king is.
事实上他是唯一一个 不是真正国家元首的国家元首
In fact, he's the only head of state that's not an actual head of state.
国王才是
Again, king.
你们只是两个倒霉蛋
You're just two guys that are shit out of luck.
所以 走吧
So let's go.
来吧
Come on.
你们现在是我的包裹
You are now my package.
也是我的任务
My mission.
我的任务就是把你俩活着
And my mission is to deliver you alive
送到这片大陆上最安全的地方去
to the most secure location on this continent,
也就是在得里雅斯特的北约峰会
and that is the NATO summit in Trieste.
要让任务不脱轨 这列火车就是我们最好的机会
And my best shot at keeping this mission on track is that train.
双关 这次不是故意的
Pun, this time, not intended!
你是带我们开火车的车头吗
You seem very "locomotivated"!
只是想确保计划不会脱轨
Trying to make sure this thing doesn't go off the rails!
果然如此
Ha! Well, that confirms it!
坠机时我肯定已经死了 跟你俩在一起简直是地狱
I died in that plane crash, and this is hell!
加油
Come on!
拉住你了
你还好吗
You good?
谢谢
Thank you.
你的团队在西班牙的事...
About your team in Spain.
我们都失去了很多
We've all lost a lot.
听着 我欠你...
Look, I-I owe you a...
请你不要说抱歉
Please don't say an apology.
只是想解释下 的黎波里之后我为什么消失了
An explanation for disappearing after Tripoli.
在的黎波里发生了什么
What happened in Tripoli?
不关你的事
None of your business.
继续睡觉吧
Go back to sleep.
首先 你没有在的黎波里消失
Okay, first of all, you didn't disappear in Tripoli.
你无处不在
You appeared everywhere.
你上过电视 报纸 社交媒体...
You were on TV, newspapers, social media...
- 我在竞选公职 - 你在逃避
- I was running for office. - You were running away.
是因为爱吗
Was it love?
你在逃避爱吗
Were you running away from love?
你能管好自己的事吗
Can you stay in your lane?
你本可以跟我一起
And you could have come with me.
一起参加竞选活动
On the campaign trail?
比如去上早间节目 和全世界分享我妈妈的千层面食谱
Like, go on breakfast TV and share my mom's lasagna recipe with the world?
我们本可以在一起的
We would have been together.
不 萨姆
No, Sam.
我们不可能在一起的
We couldn't have been together.
我去吃点东西 需要什么吗 总统先生
I'm gonna go get something to eat. Can I get you anything, Mr. President?
你吃什么给我带一份就行
I'll have whatever you're having.
没问题
You got it.
我可能要问越界的问题了
I'm just gonna go out on a limb here.
你们俩以前不只是同事关系对吧
You two did a little more than work together back in the day, huh?
我是说 她看起来人很好
I mean, she seems nice.
比你的最好朋友幕僚长好多了
A lot better than that best friend chief of staff of yours
- 那个卧底间谍 - 我不想和你聊这些
- that's a sleeper spy insurgent. - We're not having this conversation.
听着 伙计 她在感情上有点淡漠
Listen, man, she's a little emotionally distant.
不过很有幽默感
Great sense of humor, though.
嘿
Hey.
你们为什么分开了
Why'd you guys split up?
又来了 不停问问题
And he's back. Back to questions.
拜托 在的黎波里发生了什么
Come on. What happened in Tripoli?
- 别问了 - 在的黎波里发生了什么 萨姆
- Don't. - Come on. What happened in Tripoli, Sam?
别再说的黎波里了
Stop saying "Tripoli"!
好吧 在利比亚首都发生了什么
Fine, what happened in the capital city of Libya?
我在那里告诉了她我想竞选首相
It's where I told her that I wanted to run for office.
你满意了吗
Are you happy now?
- 你为什么想竞选  - 你还问
- And why'd you want to run for office? - Oh, God, are you still going?
你为什么想竞选 萨姆
Why'd you want to run for office, Sam?
因为我想为她打造一个更好的世界 我们可以一起在这世界里白头偕老
Because, because I wanted to build a better world for her and I to grow old in together!
这真是...
That's...
我听过的最浪漫的事
...the most romantic goddamn thing I've ever heard.
她可不是...
Yeah, well, she didn't...
她可不是这么想的
she didn't see it that way.
- 该死  - 我们可以商量一下
- Shit! - Whoa, whoa. We can talk this out.
我知道你们都很迷恋自己的声音
I know you're both enamored with the sound of your own voice,
但你们谁也不许说话了
but there's no more talking.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?!
该死
Oh, shit.
没想到会这样
Didn't see that coming.
已经来不及了
Already short on time as it is.
放下枪
Drop it.
- 嘿 别开枪 - 我们得听他解释
- Whoa, hey. Don't shoot him. - We need to hear him out.
你们想听他解释 边走边听吧
You want to hear him out? Let's do it on the move.
走吧
Come on.
我只想平静地度过余生 但格拉多夫找到了我
All I wanted to do was live my days out in peace, but Gradov found me,
强行控制住我
put his claws into me,
让我做我从来不想做的事
made me do things I never wanted to do.
但现在发生的事
But what's happening now,
我们正在做的事 已经太过了
what we've set into motion now, it's a bridge too far.
我知道你们已经察觉
I know you've figured out there's an insider
政府最高层有他的内奸 但是我...
working at the highest levels of government. And, no, I...
我不知道...
I don't know...
我不知道是谁
I don't know who the insider is.
我从没见过他们 但他们帮格拉多夫进入了“梯队”
I never saw them face-to-face. But they helped Gradov get into Echelon,
帮他摧毁了空军一号
and they helped him take down Air Force One.
我们怎么查出这个内奸是谁
Then how do we find out who this insider is?
通过格拉多夫的安全通讯
Through Gradov's secure communications.
我设计的通讯
Communications I designed.
但你们必须马上下车
But you'll have to get off this train right now.
车还在开呢
While it's moving?
格拉多夫现在拥有上帝视角
Gradov's got the eyes of God at his disposal.
他会派一队人在下一站等着杀了你们
They'll have a team waiting at the next station to kill you.
- 真棒啊 - 真棒啊
- Great. - Great.
听着 我在克罗地亚有个据点
Look, there's a building in Croatia
那时我还不认识格拉多夫
I operated out of before I ever knew the name Gradov.
去扎达尔的拉瓦斯卡街12号
Get to 12 Lavaska Street in Zadar.
五楼有个加密终端站
There's a secure terminal there on the fifth floor.
把手给我
Give me your hand.
好了
这个指令能运行我设计的一个程序
This prompt will run a program I designed
定位所有涉密许可持有者 与其通讯轨迹
to trace communications he had with anyone carrying compartmented security clearance.
运行这个程序
Run the program,
你就能找到内奸
you'll find the insider.
你们必须结束这一切
You have to end this.
格拉多夫胃口太大
Gradov is insatiable.
他永远不会停手的
He'll never stop.
做点好事改变一下感觉真好
Feels nice to do something good for a change.
该死 好吧
Shit. Okay.
好吧
Okay.
你知道吗 我们能搞定的 好吗
You know what? We got this, okay?
《亡命跳跃》里 我可是从货运列车上跳下去的
Hell, I barrel-rolled off a freight train in Death Jumpers.
你没跳 是你的替身跳的
No, you didn't. Your stuntman did.
你非得这时候跟我抠字眼
Now? Now you want to bust me on a technicality?
先生 恕我直言 没人能从这列火车上跳下去
Sir, respectfully, no one is barrel-rolling off of this train.
是时候露头了 我们得打电话求助
I think it's time to raise your heads. We have to call someone.
不行 我们得假定 所有高官都已被渗透
No, no, no. We have to assume that all high command posts are compromised.
没错 如果我们现在露面 内奸就会开始演戏
Yes, and if we resurface now, the cover-up begins,
我们永远无法知道内奸是谁 他们又能逍遥法外了
we never find out who's behind this, and they get to fight another day.
所以你宁愿 跳下时速65公里的火车吗
So you'd rather jump off a train that's going 40 miles an hour?
我们被动挨打已经太久了
We've been taking this on the chin for way too long,
我受够了一直防守
and I'm done with being on the defensive!
得了吧
Oh! Come on!
好吧 嘿
All right, hey!
记得把下巴缩到胸前
Just tuck your chin to your chest!
- 你确定有用吗  - 相信我
- Sure that's gonna make a difference? - Trust me!
我觉得他没事
I think he's okay.
真是见鬼了
Damn you.
雄起 德林杰
Man up, Derringer.
你可是美国总统
You're the President of the United States.
星条旗万岁
Stars and stripes forever!
团身缓冲
在中情局我们有个说法
At the CIA, we had a saying:
“组织之力 源于个人
"The strength of the organization is the individual.
“个人之力 成于组织”
The strength of the individual is the organization."
在座的各位 正是这一精神的鲜活体现
The collective that sits in this room is the living embodiment of that.
而某些人正企图操纵我们
And someone out there is manipulating us.
分裂我们
Trying to tear us apart.
所以让我们向幕后黑手传递一个信号
So let's send whoever's behind this a message.
一致向外
Swing in the other direction.
加倍投入北约
Double down on NATO.
让他们明白 任何破坏这一联盟的企图
Let it be known that if you try and break this bond,
只会让我们更强大
it will only make us stronger.
这些感性的话挺可爱的
Those are lovely sentiments.
但你说的这些得建立在信任之上
But what you're asking for is predicated on trust.
我不信任这房间里的任何人
And I don't trust anyone in this room.
- 总理 - 没关系
- Chancellor... - It's fine.
让他走
Let him walk.
现在是他的竞选季 他很害怕
He's in a campaign season. He's scared.
猜猜下一届竞选我要主打什么
You know what I'm going to campaign on in the next cycle?
退出这个联盟
Withdrawing from this alliance.
没关系
It's okay.
我们可以一起撑下去
We can hold this together.
美国将承担他们的那部分费用
The U.S. will cover the cost of their contribution.
这正是我们所需要的 不是吗
That's what we all need, isn't it?
我想是的
I think so.
美式傲慢又一次 被强塞进我们的喉咙
More American arrogance shoved down our throats.
明天早上将进行投票
There will be a vote held in the morning
25个国家已经同意解散北约 包括意大利
with 25 countries already on board to disband NATO, including Italy.
到时见 总统女士
I'll see you there, Madam President.
缩下巴还挺管用的吧
Man, the chin thing kind of worked, huh?
好了 可别再提下巴了
All right, enough with the bloody chin thing.
你下巴没事多亏了我的妙招好吧
You don't have a bloody chin thanks to my killer pro tip.
干得好 兄弟 你惹她生气了
Way to go, bro. You made her mad.
多谢
Thanks.
天啊 哈蒙德选藏身地的品味真差啊
Geez, Hammond didn't have an incredibly sexy taste in hideouts, huh?
有些人就喜欢躲在废弃的旧建筑里
Well, some people like to hide out in old derelict buildings,
就像有些人喜欢吸羊奶头一样
and others like to suck on sheep nipples.
- 谁吸羊奶头了  - 没谁
- Who sucks on sheep nipples? - Nobody sucks on sheep nipples!
好吧 天啊 老天爷
Okay. God. Geez.
- 几楼  - 五楼
- What floor? - Fifth.
好吧
All right.
快点 健身房强者
Come on, Gym Strong.
这里什么都没有
There's nothing here.
那个该死的王八蛋骗子
Hammond, that lying son of a bitch.
把我们骗进了死胡同
Led us to a dead end.
等等...
Unless...
他没骗我们
...he didn't.
太好了
Well, nice.
好极了
Okay.
你听到了吗
Do you hear that?
感觉来者不善啊
That does not look like the cavalry!
把自己锁在安全屋里 我来处理
Lock yourselves in the safe room. I'm gonna go handle this.
只有你能从服务器上找到情报 我来拖住他们
No, no, no. You're the only one that can get the intel off the server. I'll hold them off.
萨姆
Sam...
- 你觉得我退步了吗  - 你确实退步了
- What, do you think I've lost a step? - I know you've lost a step.
- 我只是不希望你死在我面前 - 快去吧
- I just don't want you dying on my watch. - Just go.
我们能搞定的
We got this.
你跟我来 我需要你的手
You're coming with me. I need your hand.
我中枪了
I've been shot!
你没事吧
You okay?
没事
Yep!
手
Hand.
好了
Okay.
不妙
Oh, shit.
- 他没事吧  - 拖住他们了 但我们得走了
- Is he okay? - Yeah, he's holding them off, but we need to go.
快点快点
Come on, come on, come on.
好了 进去了
Okay, we're in.
行动中止
Abort!
撤退
Fall back!
- 我找到内奸了 - 是的 是昆西
- I got the insider. - Yeah, it's Quincy.
是布拉德肖
It's Bradshaw.
胡说
Bullshit.
证据呢 给我看看
Tell me where it says that.
她和格拉多夫18个月前就开始联系了
There are dozens of communications between her and Gradov going back almost 18 months.
这里全是她留下的电子痕迹
Her digital fingerprints are all over this.
- 对不起 - 你不需要道歉
- I'm sorry. - You don't need to be sorry.
等我抓到她 我会毁了她的世界
I'm gonna grind up her world when I get my hands on...
卡住了
It's stuck.
- 你还好吗  - 没事
- You okay?! - Yes!
好的
Okay!
萨姆
Sam.
不
我们得从这盒子里出去
We need to get out of this box.
我需要你过来 快
I need you over here! Now!
- 看到那个屋顶了吗  - 看到了
- You see that roof? - Yeah.
尽量低一点 好吗
Get as low as you can, okay?
准备好
Get ready.
跳
Drop!
已经处理好了
It's handled.
她付了你额外的钱 让你收拾残局 对吧
She paid you extra to clean up loose ends, didn't she?
现在我就是残局
And now I'm the loose end.
很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我知道他对你有多重要
I know how much he meant to you.
我们之间的不完美如此美好
We had this... perfectly imperfect thing...
时间磨不淡 距离冲不散
...that didn't fade with time or distance.
知道有人爱你的一切
Knowing that someone loves everything about the way you are.
好吧 除了我的双关笑话
Well, except the puns.
萨姆讨厌双关
Sam hated those puns.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道吗 有那么一瞬间
You know, for a second there,
我以为老天搞出这些破事
I thought that the universe did all this shit,
这些糟心烂事
all this horrible shit,
全是为了把我俩重新凑一块儿
just to bring us back together.
我还很开心来着
And I was happy.
挺疯狂的 对吧
Pretty demented, huh?
刚发现我最好的朋友想杀了我
I just found out my best friend tried to kill me
还想彻底搞垮西方民主
and wants to rip the heart out of Western democracy,
所以现在有什么想法都算不上疯狂
so everything's being graded on a curve today.
是啊
Yeah.
随着决定北约命运的投票 30分钟后即将举行
...with a vote on the future of NATO set 30 minutes from now
各国领导人纷纷公开宣泄对盟友的
and with world leaders openly expressing their outrage
愤慨与怒火
and anger at their allies and friends,
这个历经75载的军事同盟 此刻似乎已站在了解体的悬崖边缘
it seems imminent that after 75 years, NATO is on the verge of collapse.
喂
Yes?
总统女士
Madam President.
谢谢你暂代我的职位
Thanks for keeping my seat warm.
威廉 你是怎么...
Will? How did you...
我马上就到
I'm coming in.
告诉我你需要什么
Tell me what you need.
我在得里雅斯特港
I'm at the Port of Trieste.
让“野兽”来接我
Send the Beast.
对了 科克 布拉德肖是内奸
Oh, and, Kirk, Bradshaw's behind this,
别让她知道
so box her out.
好的
O-Okay.
我会尽量拖延北约的投票 请务必安全到达
Um, I-I'll hold off the NATO vote as long as I can, and-and just get here safe.
总统先生
Mr. President.
见到你可太好了
You sure are a sight for sore eyes.
你先请
After you.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
感谢各位 会议将于十分钟后开始
Thank you, everybody. The meeting will commence in 30 minutes.
带他们去集合点 做好你的工作
Take them to the rally point and do your job.
别再让我失望了
Don't disappoint me again.
不是布拉德肖
It wasn't Bradshaw.
是科克
It's Kirk.
当然是副总统 总是副总统
Of course it was the vice president. It's always the vice president.
科克抓到他们了
Kirk has them.
别让他们到达北约会议现场
Don't let them get to NATO.
但布拉德肖确实在和格拉多夫联系
But Bradshaw's communications were tied to Gradov.
布拉德肖是个诱饵
Bradshaw was the decoy.
科克掩盖了自己的电子足迹
Kirk covered her tracks.
这叫应急方案
It's called contingencies.
你有你的应急方案
You have your contingencies,
我有我的
I have mine.
有人追来了
We got company!
开枪打他
Shoot him!
开枪
Take the shot!
该死 完了
Oh, sh-shit.
- 去开车  - 好的
- Take the wheel! - Okay!
好耶
Yeah!
萨姆
- Sam? - Sam?
稳住车子
Hold her steady!
好的 没问题
Okay, no problem!
你怎么还活着
How are you alive?!
别激动
Easy.
我只是保持冷静 继续前行
I just kept calm and carried on.
去帮她 这里有我
Help her. I've got this.
抱歉 伙计
Sorry, mate.
开门
Open the door!
很糟吗
Is it bad?
- 我们要去哪  - 我来了
- Where are we going? - I got you.
别第三次死在我面前好吗
Don't go dying on me a third time, okay?
我腿上有把刀
Oh, there's a knife in my leg!
等等 也许我们不该把它拔出来
No, wait, wait. Maybe we should leave it in.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- 也没那么糟 - 很好
- Wasn't that bad. - Good. Okay.
萨姆
Sam?
踩油门
Punch it!
趴下
Get down!
我在盲开
I'm driving blind here!
这里 卫星地图
Here! Sat view!
很好
Nice.
这辆蝙蝠车里还有其他玩具吗
Any other toys in this Batmobile?
烟雾
Smoke!
- 转 快转  - 这就转
- Turn. Turn. Turn. Turn! - I will. I will. I will.
冰箱
The fridge!
什么 要用零食干掉他们
What, are you gonna kill them with snacks?
备用血液
Backup blood supply.
接好了 该死的王八蛋
Take this, you bloody bastards!
是“野兽”
That's the Beast. It's the Beast!
他有火箭筒
He's got a rocket launcher!
萨姆 敌袭
Sam, incoming!
你已到达目的地
You have now reached your destination.
从今晚午夜起
Effective midnight tonight,
意大利将正式退出北约
Italy will be withdrawing from the NATO alliance.
我们也代表法兰西共和国
On behalf of the Republic of France,
正式退出
we withdraw as well.
我怀着沉痛的心情宣布 尽管我已为维系此联盟付出
It's with a heavy heart, despite my most strident efforts
不遗余力的努力
to hold this alliance together,
我代表美利坚合众国
on behalf of the United States,
宣布退...
I withdraw our...
打住
Hold it right there!
我代表英国...
On behalf of the United Kingdom...
和美国...
And the United States of America.
大家别情绪上头
...take it all down several notches, everyone.
没错
That's right.
我们可没那么容易被干掉
You're not getting rid of us that easy.
这个联盟也休想说散就散
And we're not getting rid of this alliance that easy,
因为我们都有自己的职责
because we all have a job to do.
我明白
I get it.
你们很羞愤 你们很愤慨
You're embarrassed. You're angry.
但我们需要北约 我们需要合作
But we need NATO. We need partnerships.
我们需要尊重彼此
We need to treat each other with respect,
拥抱差异
embrace each other's differences
寻求大同
and lean into our commonalities.
向子孙后代传递一个信息 那就是我们在这里
To send a message to future generations that we were here.
我们做了正确的事
That we did the right thing.
首先要做的就是
And that starts by taking the fight
向真正的敌人宣战
to the very real enemies we face.
够了
There it is.
这就是必然的结局
The inevitable conclusion.
人民选出了个蠢演员 来当自由世界的领袖
The people elect a dopey actor as leader of the free world.
这样他们的国家怎么可能存活呢
Of course their country can't survive.
你就这样轻易达成协议了
And you just sealed the deal.
这些人是我们的伙伴 我们需要他们
These people are our partners, and we need them.
需要他们做什么
For what?
我们自己种植食物 抽取石油 生产制造
We grow food. We pump oil. We manufacture.
同时 我们还得派人去帮他们打仗
Meanwhile, we send our people to die in their wars.
这不是合作关系
This is not a partnership.
我们付出 他们只会坐享其成
We give, they take.
但现在不是了
But not anymore.
航班即将坠毁
The plane is going down.
我们得先给自己戴上氧气面罩
We put the oxygen masks on ourselves first.
- 反正这些都是虚假的联盟 - 虚假的联盟
- These are all false alliances anyway. - False alliances?
看来你对此很了解啊
That's something you know a lot about.
这是你最难过的点 对吗
That's what kills you most, isn't it?
不是因为我是个比你更优秀的政治家
It's not that I'm a better politician than you'll ever be.
而是因为我是比你更优秀的演员
It's that I'm a better actor.
把他们全杀了
Kill them all.
所有人趴下
Everybody, down!
那边
Over there!
快进来
Get in here!
趴下
Get down.
去干掉她
Deal with her.
快点 我们该走了
Now! We should go now!
那边 快走
That way!
不 那边 快
No, no, no! That way! Go! Go!
格拉多夫
Gradov!
伙计们 快点 我们得走了
Guys, come on! We've got to go!
萨姆
Sam!
威廉
Will!
诺埃尔
Noel.
去追格拉多夫 我来搞定他
Get Gradov! I got this guy.
她说她搞定
She said she's got it.
走吧
Go.
开枪打他
Shoot him?
把枪拿起来
Get the gun.
瞧瞧谁才是动作片主角
Who's the action hero now, huh?
威廉
Will!
可以上了吗
Good to go?
这次别再只射墙了
Try not to kill the wall.
我打中他了
I got him. I got him.
他肯定在里面
He's got to be in here somewhere.
我觉得他没子弹了
I think he's out.
上
Let's dance.
把枪扔了
Drop it.
退后
Back up.
Back up!
你已经无处可去了
There's nowhere to go.
大结局了
It's over.
这可不是我的结局
Not for me.
该死 我们就这样让他跑了
Goddamn it! We're gonna let him get away?
十年太久 必须现在抓住他
We can't wait ten years to get this guy.
没错 十年太久
We're not waiting ten years.
你还记得《水蟒2》的结局吗
Do you remember at the end of Water Cobra 2?
你说你没看过我的电影啊
You said you never saw my movies.
我说骗你的 我全看过
I know. I lied. I've seen them all.
都是经典之作
They're classics.
但最最震撼人心的一幕
But the one moment that really cut through them all
是“水蟒”牺牲自己来拯救他的兄弟
is when Water Cobra sacrifices himself to save his brother.
你知道我在说什么吗
You know what I'm talking about?
数到三
We go on three?
三
Three!
我这个健身房强者如何
How's that for gym strong?
嘿
Hey!
“箭”出必有因
Everything harpoons for a reason.
北约濒临解散两个月后
Two months after NATO nearly disbanded,
该联盟在重建信任方面 迈出了令人鼓舞的进展
the alliance is making hopeful strides in rebuilding trust.
德林杰总统与克拉克首相 在推行新型透明度机制中
President Derringer and Prime Minister Clarke have been crucial in these efforts,
起到了关键作用
as new transparency measures are being implemented
各方正逐步重拾协同共识
and there's a restored sense of cooperation.
- 你的酒 - 多谢
- Here you go. - Cheers.
真不错
Nice.
你们俩要再续前缘了吗
You two gonna rekindle?
我不知道
Uh, I don't know.
她正在世界各地执行机密任务
She's halfway around the world on some covert operation.
看看接下来怎么样吧
We'll see how it goes.
还是有点复杂 知道吗
Still a bit complicated.
只要让她多看优点 少看缺点
Well, just talk her out of the cons and into the pros.
也许她会回心转意的
Maybe she'll come around.
其实
Actually...
你能帮我看看这条怎么回
you might be able to help me with this.
“恭喜你支持率飙升
"Congratulations on your big bump in approval ratings.
看来你的民调 也没你想的那么‘民掉’啊”
Guess you're not as poll-arizing as you thought."
- 好吧 我们也用双关回她 - 好吧
- Okay, so now we got to hit her with a pun back. - Okay.
这样吧...“确实还行 但和你比还是不够‘屌’啊”
Uh, it's, um, it's, uh... "That's nice, but it polls in comparison to you."
你知道吗
You know what?
我还是就回“谢谢”好了
I think I'm just gonna go with: "Thank you.
“我想念你
I miss you.
希望很快能见到你
Hope to see you soon.
别中枪了”
Don't get shot."
你猜怎么的 这回复太完美了
You know what? That's perfect.
免得等下我忘了
Before I forget,
两张哈里斯泰尔斯 华盛顿歌友会的票
two tickets to a meet and greet with Harry Styles in D.C.
说真的 现在你是最酷的 萨姆大叔了
It's official. You are now the coolest Uncle Sam I know.
谢谢 饿了吗
Thank you. You hungry?
饿死了 有什么好吃的
Oh, I'm starving. What's good here?
我给我们点了些吃的
I ordered us a little something.
请慢用 先生们
Here you go, gents.
好吧
Okay. All right.
炸鱼薯条
Fish and chips.
吃吧
Dig in.
你们...什么 没有番茄酱
You guys, um, got any, uh, ketchup?
没有 我们加醋
No. We do vinegar.
这是薯条 又不是沙拉
Yeah, these are fries. This is not a salad.
我的国家 我的调味品
Well, my country, my condiments.
好吧 知道吗
Okay. Okay. You know what?
等你来椭圆办公室的时候 我们得配番茄酱
Well, you come to the Oval Office, we're doing ketchup.
一旦你改变主意 你就会被...
Once you see the light, you're gonna be stocking the, um...
你的办公室叫什么名字来着
What the hell's your office called again?
- 我的办公室  - 对
- My office? - Yeah.
就叫我的办公室
It's called "my office."
你们真的是很乏味啊
Boy, you guys are really afraid of spicing things up, huh?
是啊 用颜色和形状来命名真的很辣
Oh, yeah. It's really spicy to name things after colors and shapes.
- 你知道我的意思 -“我们该怎么称呼这个白房子
- You know what I mean. - "Hey, what should we call this white house?
- 白宫 ” - 住嘴吧
- Mm, the White House?" - Don't.
“这间办公室是椭圆形的 我们应该叫它什么
"Hey, this office is oval. What should we call it?
- 我知道了 就叫椭圆...” -“椭圆办公室”
- I know." - The Oval Office.
- 真辣啊 - 对
- Yeah, yeah. - That's real spicy.
你有意见吗 去跟乔治华盛顿说啊
Hey, you got a problem, take it up with George Washington, okay?
他在椭圆办公室 建成前100年就去世了
He died a hundred years before the Oval Office was even built.
为什么非要跟我较真
Uh, why you gonna bust me on a technicality?
- 较真来说 这不算较真 - 这只是无关紧要的细节
- Well, technically it's not a technicality. - It's an insignificant detail.
不 这是事实 这才是需要较真的地方
No, it's a fact, which is exactly what a technicality is.
你什么时候成为农民的  你要把笑点榨干了
When did you become a farmer? 'Cause you are milking this.
真的吗 什么时候轮到 你这个羊奶头爱好者来说我了
Really? Says you, the sheep nipple aficionado?
这事就不用再提了吧
I don't even think we need to talk about that.
- 不想提这个吗  - 不想
- You don't want to talk about that? - No. No, we don't.
我为民众吃枪子了吗
Did I take one for democracy?
当然了 脑袋中了一枪
You bet I did. Right in the noggin.
但谁会想到呢 这颗子弹正好击中
But who would've thunk it? This bullet hit at the exact spot where
我当初因为烤架翻车事件 植入的金属板
I had the metal plate installed after my whole rotisserie grill debacle.
要是当初打偏哪怕一纳米 我都没法在这喝“巴哈马妈妈”了
I mean, one nanometer either way, I am not here sipping this Bahama Mama.
绝无可能 长官
No, sir.
我是英雄吗
Am I a hero?
当然 不定时跟总统和首相聊天时
Sure. Yeah, that's what the president and prime minister say
他们都说我是英雄
whenever we talk on a semi-regular basis.
是的 都是些关于内阁任命的小闲聊
And yes, there's some light chitchat about a cabinet appointment.
没什么大不了的
No big deal.
- 是啊 - 当然了
- Yeah. - Sure thing.
不错的尝试
Nice try.
我相信你
I believe you.
很高兴认识你 科米尔探员
Nice to meet you, Agent Comer.
国家元首